

# **CHARLIE GOODLAND**

### Bricklayer

Andover SP10 1HB

charliegoodland401@hotmail.co.uk

07827917779

I am a very hardworking individual. I enjoy exploring things I haven't come across before. I am willing to learn new things and co-operate as part of a team. I enjoy hands on activities and I like to get stuck into any situation given to me. I am extremely adventurous. I am a very outgoing person with a strong personality, I am a very helpful person. I have grown up in a very well mannered family and know my limits. I aspire to be a lot like my dad who has skills in pluming, electrics, brick laying but mainly specialises in carpentry. I've been studying construction based subjects for 5 years now so i am well aware off all the things you should and should not do on a construction site.

Photography - GCSE C
Photography - BTEC First Pass
English - GCSE C
Science - GCSE C
Art - GCSE B
Carpentry & joinery diploma level 1 -PASSED
bricklaying diploma level 1 - distinction
Level 2 diploma brickwork - distinction

CITB - CSCS card - PASS

#### Interests and Achievements

I am very interested in outdoor activities and physical activities. One of my main interests is extreme sports, I specialise in BMX and MTB. I'm also have started my scuba diving training. I plan to carry on traveling the world through my life as much as I can. Currently I'm looking for job that can offer me something new and exciting.

#readytowork

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Bricklayer

Persimmon Homes - Andover

2016 to Present

I currently work here as part of a trainee gang but have proved to myself and to other collages that this isn't the place for me!!!! But have worked my hardest and used this time to improve my skills on timber frame builds

#### **Fencer**

Chariot Fencing - Oxfordshire

June 2016 to November 2016

For this job role i was a labourer/fence erector for chariot fencing. Roe included general labouring duties including keeping site tidy and doing anything i could to keep the tradesmen ready to do what they needed to. other duties included making out, digging holes for post moving materials and erecting fences with tradesman.

#### **Labourer - Part Time**

**G & R cousins** - Andover February 2016 to July 2016

#### Labourer

#### **Teddy Build**

August 2014 to September 2014

Whilst working on this job I had the duty to fit kitchen cabinets, the main oven, the kitchen sink. I also fitted the kitchen tiles across the walls. Main responsibilities were to make sure that it was done properly because the customer we were working for had a severely disabled son, so I and the other workers felt we needed to complete the job to benefit him. Also I've been been a labourer for a small building company, were we renovated an old cottage in a little village around Andover area.

## **EDUCATION**

#### **Andover College**

September 2014 to 2016

#### **John Hanson Community School**

September 2009 to July 2014

### **SKILLS**

- Driving (3 years)
- CSCS CARD (3 years)

#### CERTIFICATIONS AND LICENSES

# **Full UK Driving Licence**

February 2017 to Present

# **ADDITIONAL INFORMATION**

# Key Skills

- Friendly
- Good with IT
- Handling/Lifting
- Problem solving
- Good time keeper
- Construction as a whole
- Carpentry
- Bricklaying
- Landscaping
- Determined
- Adventurous

# Fencing

- Great working as a team member
- I get the job Done
- A good laugh (at the appropriate times)